ethnews.com 2018-08-29

# Privacy Policy - ETHNews.com

Thank you for visiting ETHNews.com ("the Service," "we" or "us"). Your privacy is important to us. This privacy policy only covers this website. Websites linked to from this site are not covered by this policy. Please be alert when you leave our site and read the privacy statements of each and every website that collects personally identifiable information. This Privacy Policy, as amended or otherwise changed from time to time (the “Privacy Policy”), explains the manner in which we collect, use, maintain and disclose user information obtained through the Service. By using the Service, you (“User”) consent to the data practices prescribed in this Privacy Policy. On occasion, we may revise this Privacy Policy to reflect changes in law, our personal data collection and use practices, the features on the Service, or advances in technology. If material changes are made to this Privacy Policy, the changes will be prominently posted on the Service. Capitalized terms not defined herein shall have the meanings ascribed to them in the Terms of Use.

 **1\. What information do we collect?**

If you open an account to utilize the forums or the trollbox on the Service, we will collect your email address. Posting comments on the Service requires registration with a third-party. We do not have any access to the personal information that you provide to that third-party, other than your user name, which will be displayed publicly on our site. If you choose to register so that you may post comments, please read the privacy policy of the third-party to whom you are providing personal information in connection with the registration process. We also collect passive information which includes, but is not limited to, IP addresses, referral URLs, your location, and other session data.

 **2\. How do we use the information we collect?**

The personal data we collect will not be given or sold to any third parties. We may use the personal data and information we collect: a) to enforce the legal terms (including without limitation our policies and terms of service) that govern your use of our Service, and/or for the purposes for which you provided the personal data; b) to provide technical support for the Service; c) to prevent fraud or potentially illegal activities (including, without limitation, copyright infringement) on or through the Service; or d) to protect the safety of our Users.

 **3\. When would we disclose the information we collect?**

We may disclose the information we collect: a) in response to legal process, for example, in response to a court order or a subpoena, a law enforcement or government agency's request or similar request; or b) to third parties in order to investigate, prevent, or take action (in our sole discretion) regarding potentially illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to any person, us, or the Service, or violations of our policies, the law or our Terms of Use, to verify or enforce compliance with the policies governing our Services. Other than as stated in this Privacy Policy, we do not disclose any of your personal information to third parties unless required to do so by law enforcement, court order, or in compliance with legal reporting obligations.

 **4\. Retention of Personal Information**

You can update your information by contacting support at support@ETHNews.com. 

We will retain your information for as long as your account has not been closed or as needed to provide you access to your account. If you wish to close your account, contact us at support@ETHNews.com. We will retain and use your information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our Terms of Use.

 **5\. How do we use cookies?**

We collect web browser information in order to enhance your experience on the site and track how the Service is being used. Cookies are small data files that are stored on your computer’s hard drive, and in addition to using cookies to provide you with a better user experience, we use cookies to identify and prevent fraudulent activity. These cookies contain no information intended to identify you personally. The information collected can include, but is not limited to, your IP address, referral URLs, the type of device you use, your operating system, the type of browser you use, geographic location, and other session data. Cookies are not permanent and will expire after a short time period of inactivity. You may opt to deactivate your cookies, but it is important to note that you may not be able to access or use some features of our site. We are not responsible and we cannot be held liable for any loss resulting from your decision or inability to use such features.

 **6\. How do we protect your personal information?**

We take the protection of your personal information seriously. We use industry-standard data encryption technology and have implemented restrictions related to the storage of and the ability to access your personal information. ETHNews.com servers and business operations are entirely located in the United States. Please note that no transmission over the Internet or electronic storage method is guaranteed to be 100% secure.

 **7\. Contact Information**

If you have any questions about the foregoing Privacy Policy as outlined above, please contact us at support@ETHNews.com. 

This Privacy Policy was last updated on May 27, 2016.
